carrotink.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy | Carrot Ink

**Privacy Policy - Effective January 27, 2012**

Carrot Acquisition Partners LLC (“Carrot Ink”) is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of the personally identifiable information you share with us (the phrases "personally identifiable information" or "personal information" mean any information by which you can be identified, such as your name, email address, address, telephone number, etc.). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information or personal information we may collect from you when you visit our web site, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review and correct, the information, as well as our policy limiting any potential sale or transfer of ownership of such information. This policy applies only to users accessing our web site from the United States.

As a part of our commitment to your privacy, Carrot Ink supports and adheres to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association's "Privacy Promise to American Consumers." We have agreed to: (1) provide customers with the notice of their ability to opt out of information rental, sale, or exchange with other marketers; (2) honor customers' requests not to share their information with other marketers; and (3) honor customers' requests not to receive mail, telephone, or other solicitations from Carrot Ink.

## **Collecting Information About You**

****In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but individual users will remain anonymous, unless you voluntarily tell us who you are.

**Using Information About You  
**We use the personally identifiable information you provide for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order, subscription or registration, analyzing trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services, and offers, and providing you with information from and about Carrot Ink. Credit card information is used only to process your order when your order is ready to ship. From time to time, we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours. These are known as our Marketing Partners. In such cases, we might share and cross-reference information, including personally identifiable information about you, which will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online and over the telephone. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our Marketing Partners and others. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

We may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services, including credit card processing, shipping, data management, promotional services, etc. We call them our Service Providers. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. We also ask our Service Providers to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours.

**Editing, Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Information About You – “Opt-Out”  
**We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. At any time, if you prefer not to receive information from us or from our Marketing Partners, please let us know by calling us at toll free (877) 322-7768 or by sending us an email at [privacy@carrotink.com](mailto:privacy@carrotink.com). Please be sure to include your email address, full name, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. If you would like to update or correct your email address, street addresses, or other personal information with us, please contact us by email at [privacy@carrotink.com](mailto:privacy@carrotink.com).

In addition, when you purchase from us online, via the telephone, facsimile, or postal mail, or when you choose to enter a sweepstakes or other promotion, we may need to contact you via phone, email, or mail to address questions or issues specific to your order, entry, etc., even if you have opted to not receive communications.

Please remember, if you delete certain information, you may not be able to continue to purchase products or access other portions of our web site without entering that information again.

**Limitations on Sale / Transfer  
**Should circumstances arise which give opportunity for your personal information to be sold or transferred, Carrot Ink will not sell, share, or otherwise disclose covered information to an unaffiliated party without first obtaining the express affirmative consent of the individual to whom the covered information relates.

**Protecting Children  
**Carrot Bunch Companies takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of children. Our web site is a general audience site. We do not permit anyone under the age of 13 to register with us. We also do not send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13 without their parent's consent.

Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any personal information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children's access to the web.

**Cookies  
**Our web site uses "cookies." A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products and services to suit your personal interests, estimate our audience size, track visits to and sales at our store, and process your order, track your status in our promotions, contests and sweepstakes, and/or analyzing your visiting patterns. You can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

We also use pixel tags – tiny graphic images – to tell us what parts of our web site you have visited and/or to measure the effectiveness of any searches you may do on our site. Pixel tags also enable us to send you email in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us.

We also may contract with other companies who use cookies or other online tools such as pixel tags to measure the performance of a marketing effort on our behalf. We prohibit these companies from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Carrot Ink.

**How We Use Email  
**When you provide us your email address, we may send you emails necessary to process your order or respond to a request. For example, after you place an order at carrotink.com, you will receive an email confirmation of your order, and in most cases an email with package tracking information.

It is our intent to send you promotional email (our Email Newsletter, product promotions, and “you may be running low” reminders) if you provide us with an email address. Instructions on how to unsubscribe are included in each promotional email we send. You may also unsubscribe from all of our promotional mailings by sending an email to this address: [unsubscribe@carrotink.com](mailto:unsubscribe@carrotink.com).

Asking to be removed from Carrot Ink’s Promotional E-Mail List will not prevent you from receiving e-mail communications relating to any online order you place at Carrot Ink or other operational e-mail communications.

**Links to Third Party Sites  
**Our web sites may contain links to web sites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before disclosing any personal information on such site.

**Policy Changes  
**From time to time, we may use customer information for unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change, we will post these changes on our web site. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically.

**Your Feedback  
**To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, please give us your feedback. You may email at [service@carrotink.com](mailto:service@carrotink.com) us or write to us at Carrot Ink – Privacy Director, PO Box 2606, Addison, TX 75001.
